humyo.de 2007-11-30

# humyo.com - Privacy Policy

HUMYO.com Ltd. ("HUMYO") is committed to protecting the privacy of its customers, visitors, users, and others who use www.humyo.com or other web sites owned or operated by HUMYO (the "HUMYO Sites") 

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the HUMYO Terms of Use. Your use of the HUMYO Sites and any personal information you provide on the HUMYO Sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the HUMYO Terms of Use. 

#### The Information We Collect 

You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to HUMYO when choosing to participate in various activities on the HUMYO Sites. 

When you visit the HUMYO Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. 

Please note that any video, audio, image, or other content file you choose to share on HUMYO becomes published content and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. 

#### How We Use The Information 

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the HUMYO Sites, then we use your personal information to operate, improve, and provide to you the features and functionality of the HUMYO Sites. 

We use cookies to remember your HUMYO account information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit and if you have requested your login information be stored the next time you visit the HUMYO Sites. 

We will not share your personally identifiable information with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

We may use your email address without further consent for to contact you for the purposes of maintaining and to notify you of important information relating to your HUMYO account. 

Your name may be shared with other humyo users, you may specifiy a screen name or handle as your name. 

#### International Users 

The HUMYO Sites are hosted in the United Kingdom and are intended for and directed to users in the European Union. If you are a User accessing the HUMYO Sites from outside the United Kingdom, through your continued use of the HUMYO Sites, which are governed by United Kingdom law, you are transferring your personal information to the United Kingdom and you consent to that transfer. 

#### Merger or Sale 

In the event that HUMYO is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. 

#### Changes and updates 

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the HUMYO Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions. 

#### Date Last Modified 

This Privacy Notice was last modified October 3, 2007. 

#### Contact Information 

Should you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, you should contact us .
